Guide to the Yasser Alwan Collection AD.MC.002
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Series II: Egypt, 1895-1971; 585 (Box 1-7)
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series, 1405
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Three men leaning out the window of a train car, with a conductor standing below them. 8.9 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid655; 1089; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Trains; Photographic Prints; Railways; Berlin, Germany; Group Portraits; Transportation; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A man in a striped suit and hat standing view point overlooking the city. 6.5 x 6.2 cm, October 1937; cuid656; 1090; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Budapest, Hungary; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Hats; Men; Facial Hair
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman seated at an outdoor table set for tea/coffee. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid657; 1091; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Food; Women; Restaurants/bars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Drinks/Beverages; Berlin, Germany; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushy Beg at a race course with a binocular bag. 6.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid658; 1092; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Binoculars; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Animals; Photographic Prints; Horse Racing; Horses; Berlin, Germany
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a hat sitting on the trunk of a convertible. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid659; 1093; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Individual Portraits; Cars/Trucks; Countryside/Rural; Berlin, Germany; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Photographic Prints; Transportation
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting in the driver's seat of a convertible. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid660; 1094; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Photographic Prints; Architecture; Individual Portraits; Buildings; Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks; Women; Hats; Transportation
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg on the beach. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid661; 1095; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Men; Beaches; Germany
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and another man standing in a garden. 6.5 x 6.0 cm, October 1937; cuid662; 1096; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Architecture; Men; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Budapest, Hungary; Group Portraits; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting on the door of a convertible. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid663; 1097; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Photographic Prints; Cars/Trucks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Flags; Buildings; Individual Portraits; Women; Germany; Transportation
    - Hussein Bek Rushdy Series - The 1936 Berlin Olympics, track event, Jesse Owens at the finish line. 6.0 x 8.9 cm, August 1936; cuid664; 1098; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Sports; Photographic Prints; Olympic Games; Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Crowds; Stadiums
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - The 1936 Berlin Olympic Games, with Adolf Hitler in the background. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, August 1936; cuid665; 1099; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Sports; Berlin, Germany; Audiences/Spectators; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Crowds; Men; Fascism; Hitler, Adolf; Photographic Prints; Olympic Games; Stadiums
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg standing in front of a convertible with his hand in his pocket. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; cuid666; 1100; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Germany; Photographic Prints; Cars/Trucks; Flags; Buildings; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Individual Portraits; Transportation
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a hat. (English text "To Sap I from Sap II. And all my love. 9.7.37"). 12.8 x 8.9 cm, 9 July 1937; cuid667; 1101; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Germany; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Women; Hats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg at a table with a woman and man. 8.7 x 12.9 cm, Undated; cuid668; 1102; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Germany; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Restaurants/bars; Tea/Coffee; Hats; Group Portraits
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and woman at a formal party. 12.3 x 17.3 cm, Undated; cuid669; 1103; Studio Foto Walter Aber, Berlin=Charl., Bismarckstr. 9, Ruf: Wilh (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Fur Garments; Tuxedos; Hats; Women; Men; Restaurants/bars; Photographic Prints; Berlin, Germany; Jewelry; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and a woman in a photo booth. 5.3 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid670; 1104; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Germany; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman in a white dress sitting on a bench at a racecourse. 6.0 x 6.1 cm, Undated; cuid671; 1105; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Women; Sports; Individual Portraits; Horse Racing; Horses; Berlin, Germany; Animals; Stadiums
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg sitting at a table drinking with a woman, both wear formal attire. 12.5 x 17.4 cm, Undated; cuid672; 1106; Studio Foto Walter Aber, Berlin=Charl., Bismarckstr. 9, Ruf: Wilh (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Cigarettes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bow Ties; Tuxedos; Jewelry; Restaurants/bars; Alcohol; Men; Women; Photographic Prints; Berlin, Germany; Drinks/Beverages; Bags/Purses; Group Portraits
    - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A newspaper clipping with a picture of Hussein Rushdy Beg. 16.9 x 12.6 cm, Undated; cuid673; 1107; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Newspaper Clippings; Arabic Writing; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Newspapers/Magazines
  - Kowkab Lutfi Series, 1406
    - A mosque with wagons and a car outside. Same mosque as ref539. 12.5 x 16.9 cm, Undated; cuid515; 948; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Horses; Carriages/Coaches; Cars/Trucks; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Animals; Photographic Prints; Mosques; Religious Sites; Buildings; Transportation
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A bearded man wearing a tarbouche. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid696; 1130; Studio Photo Cavouk, 53 Rue Choubrah, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Fezes/Tarbouches
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman wearing a white fur collar and holding a bouquet of flowers. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; cuid697; 1131; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Individual Portraits; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Egypt; Fur Garments; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman in a dark dress with a light collar. 13.3 x 8.3 cm, 15 March 1921; cuid698; 1132; Studio Alban, Alexandrie, 13 Rue Fouad (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Women; Jewelry; Postcards; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Studio Photography
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman wearing a pearl necklace. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 15 February 1928; cuid699; 1133; Studio Nadir (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Head Covers/Veils; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Women; Signatures; Jewelry; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - Two women wearing coats, holding hands. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 1930; cuid700; 1134; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Fur Garments; Egypt; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman sitting on a bench, wearing a black head wrap. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 1929; cuid701; 1135; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Women; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Studio Photography; Jewelry; Painted Backdrops; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman in a dark dress leaning on a chair in front of a painted backdrop. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 1928; cuid702; 1136; A.S. Milionis, Alexandria (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Jewelry; Women; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Furnishings; Alexandria, Egypt
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman wearing a dark dress sitting on an ornate chair. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, 2 Novemeber 1920; cuid703; 1137; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women; Jewelry; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Egypt
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A hand-painted portrait of three girls wearing oufits with monograms. 8.5 x 13.5 cm, Undated; cuid704; 1138; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; Girls; Egypt; Children; Painted Backdrops; Group Portraits
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman with four children, sitting on a bench. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; cuid705; 1139; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Egypt; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Boys; Children; Painted Backdrops; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman wearing a dress with detailing around the neckline. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 1926; cuid706; 1140; Studio Photo Ramses, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Individual Portraits; Cairo, Egypt
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman wearing a long necklace. 13.4 x 8.6 cm, 27 August 1927; cuid707; 1141; Studio - Dores, Alexandrie (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Egypt; Jewelry
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young man in a suit with a bow tie, and a book in his hand. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 20 October 1915; cuid708; 1142; Studio M. Sabongi, Bakawy Street, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Bow Ties; Books; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman with a girl sitting on a column. 13.4 x 8.2 cm, Undated; cuid709; 1143; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Children; Photographic Prints; Jewelry; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Egypt; Group Portraits
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A couple seated on a chair with a painted backdrop. Duplicates. 13.6 x 8.8 cm, 1920; cuid710; 1144; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Women; Men; Jewelry; Painted Backdrops; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Facial Hair
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman wearing a costume, leaning on a water pot. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, 1923; cuid711; 1145; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Egypt; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Costumes; Women; Jewelry; Arabic Writing
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - Two young women sitting on a wooden bench against a painted backdrop. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, 1925; cuid712; 1146; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Jewelry; Women; Egypt; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman sitting at an ornate table with two books. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, 1926; cuid713; 1147; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Individual Portraits; Furnishings; Egypt; Books; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman sitting in a wooden chair and a man with a tarbouche standing next to her. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 1924; cuid714; 1148; Studio Nadir (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Studio Photography; Men; Facial Hair; Egypt; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Fezes/Tarbouches; Painted Backdrops; Women; Group Portraits; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman in a dark dress with a large bow in her hair holding a purse. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, 1920; cuid715; 1149; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Women; Studio Photography; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Painted Backdrops; Furnishings; Jewelry; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bags/Purses
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - Two women in light dress sitting on a bench holding hands. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid716; 1150; Studio Photo Ottoman (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Photographic Prints; Egypt; Jewelry; Painted Backdrops; Women; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Group Portraits
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman wearing a uniform with ribbons and a medal. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 1929; cuid717; 1151; Studio El Salam (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Uniforms; Schools/Education; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Girls; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - Two girls in similar dresses standing in front of a table with a plant on it. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 1930; cuid718; 1429; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Girls; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Group Portraits; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A couple posing in front of an abstract painted backdrop. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 24 (?) 1923; cuid719; 1152; Studio Photo London, 26 Boulevard Abbas, Heliopolis (Cairo, Egypt); Studio Photo London, 13 Rue Emad El Dine, Cairo (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Jewelry; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Women; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Heliopolis, Cairo, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman wearing a fur-trimmed coat. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 1921; cuid720; 1153; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Girls; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Fur Garments; Individual Portraits; Women; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Egypt
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A man in a striped suit sitting on a stool. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, 20 June 1932; cuid721; 1154; Antoine, Albert (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Painted Backdrops; Men; Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Furnishings; Facial Hair
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A baby in a white dress and earrings sitting on a table. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid722; 1155; Studio G. Lekegian & Co, Opposite Shepheard's Hotel, Esbekieh, Cairo (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Girls; Jewelry; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Children
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman holding flowers. 13.9 x 8.7 cm, 10 (?) 1923; cuid723; 1156; Servanis, Theodore (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Arabic Writing; Jewelry; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Women; Individual Portraits
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A girl with a tarbouche and long hair. 13.7 x 8.4 cm, 26 October 1915; cuid724; 1157; Studio M. Sarbonai, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Fezes/Tarbouches; Cairo, Egypt; Girls; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Children; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A baby in a basket. 13.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated; cuid725; 1158; Studio G. Lekegian & Co, Opposite Shepheard's Hotel, Esbekieh, Cairo (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Children; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman wearing a dark jacket and pearl necklace. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, 1929; cuid726; 1159; Studio Nadir (Box 4, Folder 9)
      English Writing; Jewelry; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Women; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman in a sleeveless dress sitting on a stool. 13.3 x 8.3 cm, 1930; cuid727; 1160; Georgiladakis, M.; Studio M. Georgiladakis, Suez, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Women; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Suez, Egypt; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A faded-out portrait of a child. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid728; 1161; Studio Photo (Th.) Canton, 24 Bld Saad Zaghloul, Alexandrie (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Children; Individual Portraits; Signatures; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman in a dark dress with flowers on her lap. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, 1923; cuid729; 1162; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Arabic Writing; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A baby girl on an ornate stool. Same baby from ref765. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 29 August 1928; cuid730; 1163; Studio Nikos Pappazoglou, Cairo, Egypt; Studio Photo Nicholas Papazoglou, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Painted Backdrops; Jewelry; Girls; Individual Portraits; Cairo, Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Children; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A baby on a white shawl with rattle next to it. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; cuid731; 1164; Studio - Hilmy, Helwan (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Toys; Children; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - Two young women, one wearing a Sphynx costume and the other wearing a falahin costume. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Undated; cuid732; 1165; Studio G. Yervant, Alexandria, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Alexandria, Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Girls; Children; Regional/National Dress; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman leaning on the arm of a chair. 13.9 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid733; 1166; Studio Photo Ramses, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Clocks/Watches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Women; Cairo, Egypt; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman sitting on a bench with a book in her lap. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 1926; cuid734; 1167; Studio Photo Vartian, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Studio Photography; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Arabic Writing; Furnishings; Women; Hats; Books; Head Covers/Veils
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A man holding an open book in his hand. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 26 October 1915; cuid735; 1168; Studio M. Sarbonai, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Painted Backdrops; Men; Books; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Fezes/Tarbouches; Furnishings; Facial Hair
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman with a striped scarf, looking off camera. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid736; 1169; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Jewelry; Women
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman in a long black dress holding an open book on a table. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, 1 April 1915; cuid737; 1170; Studio Photo Parisien, G. Constanzo & Co., Alexandria, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Women; Alexandria, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Jewelry; Books; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Painted Backdrops; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A family portrait, the man is in traditional dress. Same baby from ref757. 13.6 x 8.4 cm, Undated; cuid738; 1171; Studio Photo Nicholas Papazoglou, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Regional/National Dress; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Furnishings; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Painted Backdrops; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young couple sitting on a table, holding hands. Same couple from ref765. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, 1927; cuid739; 1172; Studio Photo Ramses, Cairo, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Women; Cairo, Egypt; Men; Furnishings; Clocks/Watches; Jewelry; Painted Backdrops; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A bride and groom. 13.8 x 8.6 cm, 26 July 1930; cuid740; 1173; Mitry's Photo Studio, Cairo (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Women; Weddings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fezes/Tarbouches; Men; Women; Weddings; Weddings; Arabic Writing; Painted Backdrops; Cairo, Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Furnishings
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman with a bouquet. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, 1928; cuid741; 1174; Studio El Salam (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Egypt; Jewelry; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A group of women in front of a building. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, 1930; cuid742; 1175; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Head Covers/Veils; Hats; Women; Egypt; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Jewelry
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman seated on a bench, looking off camera. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 20 September 1929; cuid743; 1176; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Arabic Writing; Jewelry; Women; Furnishings; Egypt; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman wearing a uniform with a white apron. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, 1919; cuid744; 1177; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Women; Egypt; Nurses; Uniforms; Books; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - Three girls sitting on rocks near the shore. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, 30 April 1926; cuid745; 1178; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Photographic Prints; Houses; Arabic Writing; Beaches; Uniforms; Girls; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Students; Children
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman posing with an umbrella. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 21 March 1930; cuid746; 1179; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Umbrellas/Parasols; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Hats; Outdoors; Suez, Egypt; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A young woman looking down and off camera. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, 1925; cuid747; 1180; K. Jacob, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Egypt; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman leaning on a tall pedestal. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid748; 1181; Studio - Isidore (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Women; Painted Backdrops; Furnishings; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Kowkab Lutfi Series - A woman looking at the camera with a head cover. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid749; 1182; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)